# **IGOR PAKHOLKOV**

# LEAD SOFTWARE ENGINEER



Telegram: @CoderGosha

Email:

coder.gosha@gmail.com Web Site:

https://codergosha.com

#### **SKILS:**

#### C#

- .NET Core
- EF Core
- Dapper
- SQL
- Миграция
- .NET Framework
- -> .NET Core
- Web API
- asvnc/await
- Andriod
- Smart Watch

#### **PYTHON**

- Django
- Django-rest
- Web Api
- WebSocket
- asyncio
- QT
- Selenuim

#### **DATABASE**

- Oracle Database
- MSSQL
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- SQLite

#### **PROFILE**

I'm a Lead Software Engineer on C# and Python and I have more than 8 years of experience. I participated in the development of manufacturing real-time system tracking (level 2). I did integration with a manufacturing microcontroller (like scales). I developed part of the metal accounting system. I supported and added new features to OPC Core (OPC Unified Architecture. NET Standard).

I developed bots for copy trading orders (cryptsy exchange). I did integration API (like websocket, rest api), monitoring indicators and copy strategy with cryptsy exchange. I received and processed data (parsing) from websites with algorithm bypassing blocking.

Now, I'm developing a high load backend for a parcel delivery system.

Current projects use .NET Core and ASP .Core. I have big experience of a migration from .NET Framework to .NET Core.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### Lead backend developer, Engy — 2020 - 2022

I'm developing a high load backend for a parcel delivery system. I'm doing integration with partners API. I ported and migrated the parcel delivery system from ASP .NET to ASP .NET Core. Integration tests, performance optimization. I'm actively supporting core for Windows (IIS + Docker + MSSQL) and Linux (nginx + docker + postgreSQL).

Stack: TFS, Git. ASP .Core, EF Core, Dapper, MSSQL, PostgreeSQL, Docker

Pilot client project for postamat on python. The client used QT and worked on an embodied system (raspberry pi). Device management, bank acquiring, receiving and delivering parcels.

Stack: Python, Sqlite, PySide, Raspberry Pi

#### Senior software engineer, PSS. Software — 2018-2020

I supported and added new features to OPC Core (OPC Unified Architecture. NET Standard). I ported and migrated OPC Core from .NET Framework (Windows + MSSQL) to .NET Core (cross-platform). And I developed a microservice for the tickets bay system on ASP .Core. The company used Microsoft Azure for building and deployment.

Stack: TFS, Git. ASP .Core, EF Core, MSSQL, PostgreeSQL, Docker, RabbitMQ

# Software engineer, Data Center Automatization Company - 2014-2018

I participated in the development of manufacturing real-time system tracking (level 2) Real time collection data, analysis manufacturing processes, integration with manufacturing microcontrollers. I developed tracking systems modules. I developed and supported a data collection system from weighing devices and controllers.

# CI/CD

- Docker
- Docker Compose
- TFS

# HARDWARE & VIRTUALIZATION

- DigitalOcean
- Azure

#### **LANGUAGES**

- Russian native
- English B2

Stack: Git, SVN ASP.NET, EF, MVC, WCF, REST, SOAP, SQL, MS SQL, Oracle, UnitTests, JavaScript, C#, C++, HTML, CSS

### **EDUCATION**

# Software engineer, Cherepovets State University — 2009-2014

Software for Computers and Computer-Aided Systems

Dissertation: Data Scales - data collection system from weighing devices and controllers